(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-26T01:36:11.583415",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
一夜限りと飛び込んだ
Diving in for just a single night,
古い旅館の2号室
in room number 2 of an old inn,
燃える花火に照らされて
illuminated by burning fireworks,
睦言交わす 熱帯夜
exchanging whispers on a tropical night.
朝が来るまで側にいて
Stay by my side until morning comes,
あの人のこと忘れたい
I want to forget that person.
真夏の夜の泣き虫は
The crybaby of a midsummer night
声を殺して泣くのです
weeps with a silenced voice.
好きだから身を引くの
I'm stepping back because I love you,
ささくれた美談 丁度いい女って
a frayed bittersweet tale, calling me a convenient woman—
こういうことなの？
is that what this is?
愛してる 愛してる 愛してる 愛してる
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you,
愛してる 幸せ探し て三千里
I love you, searching for happiness 3,000 leagues away,
触れ合えど 触れ合えど 触れ合えど 触れ合えど
even as we touch, even as we touch...
彷徨う運命が また恋に狂わせる
a wandering destiny drives me mad with love once again.
第一話
[Title: Episode 1]
劣情の果て 愛なき出航
Beyond Lust: A Voyage Without Love
あともう少しで出来るはずだね
It should be ready any minute now...
こうしてぇ…あーしてぇ…これをやってぇ…
Like this... and like that... doing this...
うわぁぁぁぁぁ!!!
Aaaaaah!!!
これはぁぁぁぁぁ!!
This is...!!
ついに完成したねぇ…!
It's finally complete...!!
これがで回ればとんでもないことになるね…!
If this gets out, something terrible will happen...
みこ部長～♥
Director Miko~♥
おつかれサマンサ
Good work, what's-her-name.
いやいやマリンたん、今日も若作りしてるねぇ～
Well, well, Marine-tan, trying to look young again today~
は？
Huh?
キミもこんな時間まで仕事だったのかねぇ？娘さんが心配してるんじゃないかな？
Were you working this late too? Aren't you worried your daughter might be concerned?
あくあなら平気ですっよ
Aqua's totally fine, you know.
それより…
More importantly...
このあとどこか飲みに行きません～？？
Wanna go out for a drink somewhere after this~~??
おおいいねぇ…ちょうど行ってみたかったバーがあるんだよ
Oh, sounds nice... There's a bar I've been wanting to check out.
あの『休憩所』もすぐそばにあるんだよね…
And that "Rest Area" is right nearby, too...
いやんっ、
Eek!
部長のエッチ～！
Perverted Department Head~!
もう
Geez.
何考えてるんですかっ、ヘンタイ！
What are you thinking, pervert?!
はぁ、わからせられる！またわからせられちゃう～！！
Ah, I'm gonna get corrected! I'm gonna get corrected again~!!
マリンたんとは行かないんだけどね
I'm not going with Marine-tan, though.
なんで？
Why?
今日はこのあとあの他の部署との飲み会があってねぇ
Today, after this, there's a drinking party with another department...
へぇ～！そうなんですね！
Heh~! Is that right?!
マリンは聞いてないですけど、なんですか？
Marine hasn't heard about this, but what is it?
あの、あのあれあれね、みんながほら、行くわけじゃなくて、あの数人でほら、行くやつだから、あの、ね？
Well, you know, not everyone's going, just a few people are...
なるほど～
I see~
じゃあ、マリンも行っていいですよね？
Then Marine can go too, right?
だめだね
No way.
なんで？
Why?
あの、あれなんだよ、男のが、あの男がいっぱいいるからね、むさ苦しい所に
Well, you know, there are a lot of guys in that musty place.
マリンたんがね、女の子でみんな興奮しちゃうからね、はっ！
Marine-tan is a girl, so everyone would get all excited, ha!
確かに、マリン狙われちゃう！！！
That's true, Marine will be targeted!!!
暑苦しい男の人たちに囲まれて、飲み会の主役になっちゃう…！！
Surrounded by stuffy men, you'd become the star of the party...!!
じゃあ行きますか
Shall we go then?
絶対ダメだね、ここ、ここか、ここわね
Absolutely not, here, here, or rather here...
女か？
A woman?
先月隣の部署に来た、あの若い女か？
That young woman who came to the next department last month?
ピチピチのぉ
The fresh one?
いや違う、違うね、あの、仕事のミーティングもか、してるから、あの、他の人が来ると、困るんだよね！！
No, we're having work meetings, so if other people come, it's a problem!!
なんだぁ、そういうことですかぁ～！
Ohh, is that so~!
え、じゃああの若い女はいないんですね？？
Eh, then that young woman isn't there, right?y
まぁ、そういうことだからね、今日は無理なんでぇ、ごめんねマリンちゃん
Well, that's how it is, so today's no good. Sorry, Marine-chan.
君ももうそろそろ帰りなさい、娘さんもいるしね
You should head home soon too, you have a daughter.
それじゃあ！
See ya!
部長！！若い女に乗り換えないで！！
Department Head!! Don't replace me with a young woman!!
ちょっと、離しなさい！
Hey, let go!
いったい
Ouch!
いつになったら結婚してくれるの！！ずっとやめないで待ってるのにぃ！！
When are you going to marry me?! I've been waiting without giving up!!
ここは会社なんだから！！会社なんだよ君ここ！！
This is a company!! This is a company, you know!!
ひどい…こんなにピチピチで、可愛くて、エッチな女の子が待ってるのに、この気持ちに応えてくれないなんて…
Cruel... Even though such a fresh, cute, and perverted girl is waiting...
ピチピチではないね
You're not fresh.
結婚しろおおお！！
Marry meee!!
お落ち着きたまえマリンちゃん！
Calm down, Marine-chan!
じゃあ明日結婚する？
Then shall we get married tomorrow?
うーん、まぁそれは早すぎるかな
Umm, well, that might be too early.
じゃあいつ結婚してくれるの？？まぁあの、色々手続きとかね、あの、親への報告とかね、あの、なんやかんや、そういうのがあって、君ももう、ね、娘さんもいるしね
Then when will you marry me?? Well, you know, paperwork, parents, and you have a daughter too...
そうなんだぁ…
Is that so...
あっ、じゃあ、マリンが先に部長のご両親にご挨拶に伺いましょうか！
Ah, then shall Marine go and greet the Department Head's parents first?!
やめて欲しいねぇ！！
I'd really rather you didn't!!
え…
Eh...
ごめんねマリンちゃん、君のこと、可愛くて、エッチだとは思ってるけど――
Sorry, Marine-chan. I think you're cute and perverted, but--
えへへ！ピチピチで可愛くてエッチだなんてそんなぁ～//
Ehehe! Fresh, cute, and perverted? Oh you~//
ピチピチではないね。可愛くてエッチだとは思ってるけど、それ以上の感情はないねぇえ！！
You're not fresh. I think you're cute and perverted, but I don't feel that way!
もうキツいねぇえええ！！
That's too harshh!!
いたいけなマリンちゃんおだましやがってよぉお！！許すまじっ！！絶対許すまじいいっ！！
You tricked poor innocent Marine-chan!! Unforgivable!! Absolutely unforgivable!!
待てコラァァァア！！！！
Wait here, you bastard!!!!
ひどいっ
How cruel...
なんでみんなマリンを裏切るの…マリンちゃんこんなに尽くしてるのに…
Why does everyone betray Marine... Even though Marine-chan tries so hard for you...
これは…みこ部長の研究してるよくわからない薬…こんなものぉ！！
This is... Department Head Miko's mysterious research medicine... Take this!!
あくあは…娘のあくあはあんなに言い寄られるのに、マリンの方が絶対エッチなのに…どうして…
Aqua gets courted so much, even though Marine is definitely more perverted... Why...
あてし、恋愛とかまだ分からなくて…だから ごめんなさい…！
As for me, I don't understand romance yet... So I'm sorry...!
今日だけでもう45人目 いい加減断るのも疲れちゃったなぁ
That's already the 45th person today. I'm getting tired of rejecting people.
あてしあくあ！どこにでもいる平凡な女子高生！のはずなんだけど、毎日2桁の男子から告白されちゃってもう大変！
I'm Aqua! An ordinary high schooler! Or so I should be, but boys confess every day!
昨日なんか通りすがりの石油王にまで告白されて、もうびっくりしちゃった！
Yesterday, even a passing oil baron confessed to me, I was so surprised!
ただ普通に高校生活をりたいだけなのにどうしていつもこうなっちゃうのぉ？？
I just want an ordinary high school life, so why does it always turn out like this??
ほかにカワイイ女の子なんかいっぱいいるのにみんなどうしてあたしなんだろう…困っちゃうなぁ
There are so many other cute girls, so why does everyone pick me... It's troublesome...
でもいつかママが読んでくれた絵本に出てくる王子様みたいな…下を向いて10回クルクル回ったあとにすぐ片足立ちをしてもよろけずに愛を叫ぶことができる王子様みたいな人が現れたら…あたしも恋に落ちるんだろうなぁ…
Someday, if a prince-like person appears who can shout love without wobbling...
誰かいるわ
Someone's here.
おい 勘弁してくれよ オマエみたいな女 この俺様に相応しいわけないだろ？
Hey, give me a break. A woman like you could never be worthy of me, right?
まあ その程度のスペックで 俺様に愛を告げた蛮勇だけは認めてやるよ
Well, I'll at least recognize the audacity of confessing to me with those specs.
俺とアベックになりたいなら わずかな期待を抱いて来世にでもかけるんだな
If you want to be a couple, hold onto a sliver of hope in your next life.
絶世の美男子 紫咲シオン
[Title: Peerless Bishounen, Murasaki Shion]
おいそこに隠れてる女！
Hey, you woman hiding over there!
俺サマを視界に入れる権利を奪われたくなかったら いますぐ出てこい
If you don't want to lose the right to keep me in your sight, come out right now!
見つかっちゃった…！
Found me...!
ごめんなさい 盗み聞きするつもりじゃなかったんだけど…
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to eavesdrop...
はっ…！ 驚いたぜ…！
Hah...! I'm so surprised...
この俺サマの目を奪う女がこの世に存在するなんてな…！
That a woman who can steal my gaze exists in this world...!
オマエ、名前はなんだ？
Hey, what's your name?
あくあ、だけど…
I'm Aqua, but...
「あくあ」か… この俺サマの目を一瞬でも奪った偉業に敬意を表し、俺サマのオンナにしてやるッ！！
"Aqua," huh... In honor of your feat of stealing my gaze, I'll make you my woman!!
え…？ ごめんなさい、あたしそういうの興味ないから…
Eh...? I'm sorry, I'm not interested in that kind of thing...
な、なんだと！？正気か！？
W-What?! Are you serious?!
それじゃあ、さよなら！！
Well then, goodbye!!
待て！オマエ…！ふふっｗ オマエ… おもしれえ女だな
Wait! You...! Heh... You're an interesting woman.
じゃあ、下を向いて10回クルクル回ったあと、すぐに片足立ちして、よろけずに愛を叫ぶことができるのかやってみて！
Then try spinning around 10 times, standing on one foot, and shouting your love without wobbling!
7、8、9、10…
7, 8, 9, 10...
愛してるぜあくあ！！俺のオンナになれッ！！
I love you, Aqua!! Be my woman!!
すごい…！全然できてないのにどうしてそんなに自信満々なの！？あなたがあたしの王子様なのだね！！好きっ！！
Amazing...! Even though you can't do it at all, why are you so confident?! You're my prince!! I love you!!
気づくのが遅すぎるぜ… うふふふー あははー
You're way too slow to realize... Hehe... Haha...
シィ～オン～♥ あくあ～♥ シィ～オン～♥ あくあ～♥
Shion~♥ Aqua~♥ Shion~♥ Aqua~♥
はぁ… 忘れようと思えば思うほど、みこ部長のことを思い出してしまうわ…
Haah... The more I try to forget, the more I end up remembering Miko-buchou...
いまごろあの人はあの若い女とどこかにでかけているのかしら… なんだかそう思ったら
I wonder if she's out somewhere with that young woman right now... Thinking about that...
修羅欲求がどんどん湧き立って来る…！！修羅場起こしたいっ！！アイツらの良好な関係にっ！クソでかい亀裂を走らせたいっ！！
My desire for drama wells up inside me...!! I want to cause chaos!! I want to drive a huge wedge into their good relationship!!
よぉーし 修羅場起こしてこよぉ～っと！！そうと決まったら居ても立っても居られなくなってきちゃったわ～！
Alright! Let's go cause some drama!! Once I decide, I can't sit still anymore!
あっ、あは～い！今行きま～す！こんなときに一体誰よぉ～
Ah, haha! I'm coming! Who on earth could it be at a time like this~?
お母さん…！
Mother...!
あのこの人、あたしの彼氏なの…！
Um, this person is my boyfriend...!
どうも。
Hello.
義理の母と書いて『お母さん』。俺サマはあくあの男、シオンです。
Spelled with the mother-in-law, read as "Mother." I am Aqua's man, Shion.
紫咲シオン
[Title: Murasaki Shion]
宝鐘マリン
[Title: Houshou Marine]
お母さん…？どうしたの？
Mother...? What's wrong?
えっ、あっ、なんでもないわ～！
Eh, ah, it's nothing~!
シオンくんよくいらっしゃったわね 狭いところだけどどうぞあがってあがって…！
Shion-kun, welcome. It's tight, but please come on up...!!
お母さん！あたし自分の部屋掃除してくるからそれまでリビングでお茶でも出しといてくれる？
Mother! I'm going to clean my room, so until then, can you serve some tea in the living room?
えぇ、もちろんよ～！
Ah, of course, of course~!
もう全く！だからいつもお掃除しておきなさいって言ってるのにもう！しょうがないでしょ！さっき来るって決まったんだもん！
Good grief! That's why I always tell you to clean up beforehand! But it's decided you're coming now, so it can't be helped!
それじゃあシオン、ちょっとまっててね！
Well then Shion, just wait a moment!
あぁ、そうするぜ
Ah, I will.
どうぞ、ごゆっくり…
Please, make yourself at home...
ごめんなさいねぇ、あの娘ったらほんとだらしなくて…
I'm so sorry, that girl is really messy...
はは、大丈夫ですよ。そういうところもほっとけなくて可愛いですからね
Haha, it's fine. Even that part is unignorable and cute, after all.
えぇ、そうね…！本当…そういう所よね…っ
Yes, that's right...! True... That kind of place...
どうしました？
What's wrong?
いえ、なんでもないわ！すぐにお茶をお出しするからくつろいで待ってて
No, it's nothing! I'll bring some tea right away, so make yourself comfortable.
どうぞどうぞ。あ,あこの子ね、おかゆっていうのシオンくんネコ大丈夫かしらぁ？
Go ahead. Ah, this child is named Okayu. Shion-kun, is cat okay?
もちろん平気ですよ、あくあから聞いてます何でも食べるネコ飼ってって
Of course I'm fine. I heard from Aqua that you keep a cat that eats anything.
そうなのよ～もう本当この子ってなんでも食べるからもう困っちゃうわもうね
That's right~ Really, this child eats anything, so I'm already troubled~
俺サマも美味いもんならなんだって食べるぜ…？どっきーん
I'll eat anything if it's delicious too...? Thump.
な、なんのことかしらっ…！
W-What on earth are you talking about...!?
おもしろいねシオンくんったら
You're so interesting, Shion-kun.
あくあから聞きましたよ。これまでお一人で彼女を育てられたそうですね。
I heard from Aqua. You've raised her all by yourself until now, right?
大変だったでしょう？ まあそうねぇ…
It must have been tough, huh? Well, that's right...
大変だったけど元気に育ってくれて嬉しいわぁ…こんなイケメンでしっかりした彼氏まで連れてきてくれちゃって、母親冥利に尽きるというかなんというか…
It was tough, but I'm glad she grew up healthy... To bring home such a handsome and reliable boyfriend, it's the ultimate reward as a mother...
でもおかしいですねぇ
But it's strange, isn't it?
MRN ニュース速報
[MRN Breaking News]
お母さんほどお綺麗なら相手の一人や二人すぐに見つかる気がしますけど
If you're as beautiful as a mother, I feel like you'd find a partner or two in no time.
もうおだてたってなにも出ないわよ～
Flattery won't get you anywhere~
お母さん… お名前は？
Mother... What's your name?
どっ、どうしたの急に…
Wh-What's with you all of a sudden...
マ、マリンよ。
M-Marine.
そうか…マリンさん、いい名前だ
I see... Marine-san, that's a good name.
そうかしらぁ…どうもありがとう…
Is that so... Thank you very much...
俺サマにはわかる…
I understand...
あんたはいま恋心を踏みにじられ自分を見失っている。俺サマならあんたの心にあいた穴を埋めてやれる。俺サマだけがマリンという海を渡る一隻の船になれる…！
You've had your romantic feelings trampled and lost sight of yourself. If it's me, I can fill the hole in your heart. Only I can become a ship to cross the sea called Marine...!
な、なにを言ってるの…！
Wh-What are you saying...!
な、何を言っているの…！
What on earth are you talking about...!?
そんな…あくあを裏切るようなことできるわけが…
Such a thing... betraying Aqua, there's no way I could...
これまでたった一人で耐えてきたんだろ…？少しくらい良い思いをしてもいいんじゃないか…？
You've endured all alone until now, haven't you...? Wouldn't it be okay to have a good time for a little bit...?
そうよ…マリンはがいっぱいがんばってきたもの…あくあのためにすべて犠牲にして…すべてではないけど…
That's right... Marine has worked hard so much... sacrificing everything for Aqua... Not everything, but...
マリンだって…
Even Marine...
マリンだってまだチヤホヤされたいっ…！
Marine wants to be pampered and spoiled too...!!
若くて良い男にチヤホヤされたい！！
I want a young, handsome man to pamper me!!
脱ぎ捨てちまえ マリン。取り繕った
Strip it off, Marine. The facade of...
「優しい母親」の仮面ごと言…俺サマの前にすべてさらけ出せ…！
...a "gentle mother" mask... lay everything bare before me...!!
シオンくん…
Shion-kun...
いいえシオンっ！もう待ちきれない！！マリン…！待ちきれない！！
No, Shion! I can't wait anymore! Marine...! I can't wait!!
マリン… 海と船 どっちが欠けても出来ないようなことをしようぜ…
Marine... Let's do something where neither the sea nor the ship can be without the other...
それって…まさか！ あぁ、そのまさかだ…
Could that be... no way! Ah, exactly that...
出航ー！！
Set sail!!
シオン〜！部屋片付け終わったから来ても大丈夫…
Shion~! I'm done cleaning the room, so it's okay to come...
シオンっ！シオン〜！！ あぁっ それをそんなっ！そんなものをこんなにしたらっ！！ マリンのバミューダトライアングルがぁっ！！
Shion! Shion~~!! Ahh, don't do that to that! If you do that to something like that!! Marine's Bermuda Triangle...!!
お母さん…？
Mother...?
はっ！！
Ha!!
お母さん…シオン… なにしてるの…？
Mother... Shion... What are you doing...?
後編へ続く
[To be continued in Part 2]
マリン船長の番組
Captain Marine's Show
はいというわけで！ 宝鐘マリン活動2周年ありがとうございます！
Hey everyone! Houshou Marine's 2nd anniversary, thank you very much!
今回はですね、ちょっと趣向を変えまして、
This time, we've changed things up a bit,
これから4コーナーあります。もう既にね、地獄の1コーナー目を見せたあとなんですけども、
and there are 4 corners coming up. We've already shown the hellish first corner,
もうここからね、4コーナーありまして、ちょっとね普段の生放送ではできないようなちょっといろんな編集を入れた、なんか番組仕立てのちょっと企画、詰め合わせみたいな感じになっているので、
with edits you couldn't normally do in a live stream, like a TV show segment package,
皆さんがね、笑顔になってくれたら嬉しいなと思っております。
I hope everyone can smile and enjoy it.
告知もね、もうちょっと結構マリンの中で重大な告知もありますので、最後までね、しっかり見てください！
There are also some major announcements from Marine toward the end, so make sure to watch until the end!
はいこのね、前半に見てもらったドラマの続きね、誰も続き見たくないかもしれませんがい、
Now, as for the continuation of the drama from the first half—nobody might want to watch it, but—
ちゃんと最後のほうに続きがあるので、最後の結末をお楽しみになー！！
there's a continuation at the very end, so look forward to the finale!!
それではー、次のコーナーへ、出航ー！！
And now, onto the next corner... Set sail!!
いらっしゃいませー！マリンのラーメン屋さんへ、ようこそー！
Welcome! Welcome to Marine's ramen shop!
はいというわけで今日はね、ラーメン屋さんをね…本日開店！
So today, we're opening a ramen shop...
今日ね開店します。
Grand opening today! Opening today.
バイトのメスガキです。はい、バイトのメスガキもいます。
There's a bratty part-time girl. Yes, there's a bratty part-time girl too.
はいそれでは早速ね、ちょっとまだ全然よくわかってないけど、いきなり5分チェ…
Alright, so let's get right into it—though I still don't really get it—
あっ、ビールもあるね。5分チェンジやっていきましょう。ほい。
suddenly a 5-min cha— oh, there's beer too. Let's do the 5-minute challenge. Here we go.
さあ、あっ！応援してる！！メスガキが！！お前働け！！あ、よしよしよしよし
Now, ah! She's cheering me on! That brat! You go to work! Ah, okay, okay, okay!
はいはいはい、ラーメンをね作りますと、これはもうフィーリングでね、フィーリングで察しがつく。はいこう、
Alright, when making ramen, you just go by feel, you can figure it out by feel. Right, like this—
あ、こうして、えーのり、のりに、こうで、あ、いらっしゃい！あー！決まった！
Ah, like this, with seaweed, like this, and— oh, welcome! Ah, nailed it!
はいはいはいはいはい、あーちょっと待って待って！いらっしゃい！
Alright, alright, alright— ah, wait, wait! Welcome!
おお、これであれが、やばい！敵が来た敵が来た！ちょ、まずい、まずい。
Oh, and then— oh no! Enemies are coming, enemies are coming! Wait, this is bad.
まだ、招き猫アタック！にゃあ！決まった！決まった招き猫アタック！
Still— Maneki-neko attack! Meow! Nailed it! Nailed the Maneki-neko attack!
ええっと、なんか、忙しいな。ええと、まあ、皆さんね、ご存知の通りね、マリンはなんですか、え、怒ってる？なに、サラリーマン？
Um, man, this is busy. Well, as you all know, Marine is— wait, are they angry? What, a businessman?
ちょっと短期なサラリーマンだな。ちょっと
He's a bit of an impatient businessman.
え、また来たが！ちょ、待って！招き猫アタック！なに、ロボット来たロボット！
Eh, another one came! Wait! Maneki-neko attack! What, a robot came, a robot!
なに、怒んないていまできた！いまできた！いまできたのに！
Hey, don't get mad, it just got done! It just got done! Even though it just got done!
じゃあこれちょっともったいない、俺食べる？これもったいないから、
Well, this is kind of a waste, should I eat it? Since it's a waste—
あ、待って！お前お前これこれこれ！ちょ、待って！来てる来てる来てる！
Ah, wait! Hey, hey, this, this, this! Wait, they're coming, coming!
ういっ！ちょ、待って！もう疲れたんだけど！ええと、
Ugh! Wait! I'm already exhausted! Um—
あー！待って！待って待って待ってやばい、こげてるこげてるこげてる！あ、できた！できたじゃん今！
Ah! Wait! Wait, wait, wait, oh no, it's burning, burning, burning! Ah, it's done! It's done right now!
ねえ、まあ全部じゃあ今！んーもうでも、短期なデブだなあ！おいおいおい！
Hey, well all of them right now! Ugh, but what an impatient glutton! Hey hey hey!
あーごと、ごと来た！ごと来た！ごと来た！ごと！ええと
Ah— another one came! Another one! Another one! Um—
こしょうアタック！あー、こしょうじゃ効かない！フライパンアタック！よし、よし、
Pepper attack! Ah, pepper doesn't work! Frying pan attack! Okay, okay—
ええと、がんばって！フライパンなくなっちゃったよ！
Um, hang in there! The frying pan's gone!
待って、しかもこいつじゃないし！こっちだ！はい！なんでもさまになって！きただ！
Wait, and it's not even this guy! It's this one! Yes! Looking the part! It came!
はじめてに！きた！はーどだなラーメン屋って！
For the first time! It came! Being a ramen shop owner is hard!
でもさ、でもさっきしかり船長はいね、この、メスガキ！あー！
But hey, but earlier Captain Marine was like, this brat! Ah—
えの、ありがと！飲むわ。そういとこ。
Enoki— thanks! I'll drink it. That's the kind of thing.
なんだこの店のロボット率！客が全員ロボット！あちょ、待って、なくなってる！
What's with the robot ratio in this shop! All customers are robots! Wait, it's gone!
はー！あー！ロボットだし、いっか、ロボットだし！あ、もうちょっと！
Ha! Ah! They're robots, oh well, they're robots! Ah, almost!
はいというわけでね、その謎の1回戦目が終わったところで、
Alright, so after that mysterious first round,
ちょっとね色々と反省点に気づきましたので、それをね完全に直して完璧なねラーメン屋をやっていこうなっ！！あー！というわけでじゃあ
I noticed various things to improve, so I'll completely fix those and run a perfect ramen shop!! Ah! So anyway,
5分チャレンジいきます！はい、まずね、なんていったって、ビールを冷やすよ、ビール！
Let's go for the 5-minute challenge! Right, first of all, we gotta chill the beer, beer!
ビールをね、あ、なんだ、離れない、これビールが離れない！おい、離れろ！あ、できたできた。
The beer— ah, what, won't let go, the beer won't let go! Hey, let go! Ah, there we go.
ラーメンも冷やしとく？まあ6本冷やしとけば、えい、えい、しこたま、ええ、あ、はいはいはいはい、餃子
Should I chill ramen too? Well, if I chill 6 bottles, ei, ei, plenty, eh, ah, alright alright, gyoza
ろっこ
Six.
えー、んと、この月に、この月に汁を入れて、待って、でき、できできでき...
Um, put broth in this bowl... Wait, it's coming, coming, coming...
マアアアアッ！！！ あああーっ！
Noooo! Aaaaaah!
2こ
Two.
まあああ！あ、できたのに、あ、そうそうあって
Whaaa! Ah, I made it! Ah, wait, that's right...
ねえなんで？ねえなんで？ちょっと待ってえっと
Hey why? Hey why? Wait, um...
待って、落ち着いて、落ち着いて、ショウキョウと取り戻して
Wait, calm down, calm down, grab the ginger and get back on track.
ここから、ここから気を取れ直して行こう
Let's pull ourselves together from here.
あ、冷やしてる、冷やしてる
Ah, chilling it, chilling it.
バッチリ冷えてますよ
It's nicely chilled, you know.
はい、どうぞ
Here you go.
ちょっとここまでちょっとミスしちゃったけど、こっから気を取り直して、完璧にね
I made a few mistakes up to here, but let's do it perfectly from here on.
え、のり
Um, seaweed.
やっぱのりはマストだな
Seaweed is definitely a must.
やっぱのりは絶対に、絶対に食べるくさい
Seaweed is definitely, definitely something you always eat.
だからのりは、もうノーシで、のりをいれる
So I'll just add seaweed without even thinking.
で、たまご
And egg.
なんだ、来たか
What, did it come?
おい！ナイス！
Hey! Nice!
あー！バッチリ！バッチリ冷えてる！
Ah! Spot on! Perfectly chilled!
ちょっと減ってきた、いつ補充する
It's getting low, when should I restock?
あ、ちょっとここ落としたけど大丈夫
Ah, I dropped some here, but it's fine.
えっとで、麺入れて、麺入れて
Um, put noodles in, put noodles in.
ねえ！あ、怒っちゃった！
Hey! Ah, they got mad!
なんだロボットって気がみじけーな
Man, robots are so short-tempered.
なんだよ、食ってんじゃねえよロボットが
What is this, stop eating, you robot.
えっと、よいしょ
Um, heave-ho.
あ、待てできた！えっと、えいっ！
Ah, wait, it's done! Um, hiyah!
ナイス！
Nice!
えー、こうで、で麺も入れて、はい、できましたと
Um, like this, put noodles in, and there you go.
あ、ビール、ビール。はい、バッチリバッチリ
Ah, beer, beer. Yep, spot on.
ちょっと客が少ないうちに、お前もか
While there are few customers... You too?
お前もか
You too?
ちょっと減ってきた
It's getting low.
まずい、減ってきた。ビールが
Crap, it's getting low. The beer is...
これ補充しとこう、補充しとこ
Let's restock this, let's restock.
おい！店が今日お前が補充しろ！おい！
Hey! You, restock the store today! Hey!
お、おお、ありがとう
Oh, oh, thanks.
サンキュー、サンキューな
Thank you, thank you.
サンキュー、まずいサンキュー
Thank you, crap, thank you.
あ、待って、汁入れて
Ah, wait, put broth in.
えっと、のり、え、卵と卵
Um, seaweed, um, egg and egg.
えー、待って、待って
Um, wait, wait.
あ、これ女の人
Ah, this is a woman.
この女とおじさんどっちが先だ？
Between this woman and the old man, who's first?
のり、麺も、またか
Seaweed, noodles... Again?
処理早い！
Processing is fast!
慣れてきた慣れてきた
Getting used to it.
こんなに、やっぱ初日だから狙われてんのかかな
Is it because it's the first day I'm being targeted?
はい、卵
Yes, egg.
くない、あっ
Not enough, ah.
うまくねえか、ちょっと覚醒してきた
Aren't I doing well? I'm kind of awakening.
ラーメン屋で勤めるまでは
Until I work at a ramen shop...
雌だけのエジドランク
Female-only edge rank?
すごい見事なバーコード
Amazing, a splendid barcode.
あ、待って、あ
Ah, wait, ah.
ビール、ビール
Beer, beer.
ビール
Beer.
ねえおじさん、ここ飲み屋じゃ
Hey mister, this isn't a pub...
ないんですよ
you know.
ねえ、ビールだけ飲みに来るってどういうことですか？
Hey, what do you mean coming just to drink beer?
えっと、のり入れて
Um, put seaweed in.
えっと、ロボットが気が短いからロボット先出して
Um, the robot is short-tempered, so serve the robot first.
冷めちゃうよ
It'll get cold.
チャーシュー
Chashu.
あ、の、待って、入ってない、入ってない
Ah, se-, wait, didn't put it in!
えー！
Eh!
ギリギリセーフ？
Barely safe?
誰かぎょうざ食べてくんない？
Won't someone eat gyoza?
余ってんですけど、冷えちゃうよね
I have leftovers, but it'll get cold.
こうで、えっと、チャーシュー
Like this, um, chashu.
はい、どうぞ
Here you go.
はあ、疲れた
Phew, I'm tired.
手伝ってよ
Help me out.
ねえ、踊ってないで手伝ってよ
Hey, don't dance, help me out.
はい、できました
Yes, it's done.
受け取るの上手
Good at receiving.
またか、なんで
Again, why?
クソな
Damn it.
あ、ロボット来た
Ah, robot came.
ロボット、ロボット、あ、麺が、麺ロボットだしっか。ロボットだから食べれるやろの精神で
Robot, robot, ah, noodles are for the robot anyway. With the mindset that since it's a robot it can eat it.
ロボットならね、この程度のね
If it's a robot, this level of...
衛生、衛生はね、大夫と、えっとこうで
Hygiene, hygiene is fine, um, like this.
はい、こうで
Yes, like this.
まずい、まずい
Crap, crap.
スクリーンショット撮っちゃった
I took a screenshot.
スクリーンショット、あ、怒っちゃった
Screenshot... Ah, they got mad.
あ、餃子
Ah, gyoza.
あ、また餃子か
Ah, gyoza again.
待って、どうしたらいい？
Wait, what should I do?
一旦とりあえずこれを完成させて
First let's complete this for now.
あっちの先だっけ？どっちが先だっけ？
Was that the other first? Which one was first?
あ、怒っちゃった
Ah, they got mad.
あ、待って
Ah, wait.
ロボットは気が短いから早く出さないと
Robots are short-tempered so I gotta serve them fast.
待って、待って
Wait, wait.
ロボット、食べて！
Eat it, robot!
ロボットお前それ
Robot, you...
ロボット食べて！
Eat it, robot!
のり、卵
Seaweed, egg.
あ、セーフセーフセーフ
Ah, safe, safe, safe.
ナイス！
Nice!
うわあ！だいぶ良くなったんじゃないですか！
Whoa! Isn't this a lot better?!
はい、というわけでさっきの試合ね、450点くらいだったんですけど
Right, so in that last match, I got about 450 points, but
今からやるのが最後の試合です
the one I'm doing now is the final match.
600点以下だった場合は、本日開店なんですけど…閉店します。
If it's under 600 points, we're open today... but we're closing down.
そのくらいね、強い気持ちでやっていこうと思うんですけど
With that kind of strong determination, I'm going to do this, but
いくつかね、気づいた点があったんでね、ちょっと紹介したいと思います。まずね、
there are a few things I noticed, so I'd like to introduce them. First off,
餃子、これ大変なんだけどこれねさっき気づいたんだけどこれ、ほら、これ皿にくっつくんだわ！これ。
gyoza, this is tough, but I just realized earlier, look, they stick to the plate! This.
こうやって皿にくっつくから、こう1個ずつ移動せずに
Since they stick to the plate like this, instead of moving them one by one,
こうやってね
like this...
えっ、ちょ、始まった…？
Eh? Wait, did it start...?
始まらない
It's not starting.
ちょっ、えっ、待てよ！待てよ！
Wait, wait! Hold on!
待てよ！
Wait!
いま、いま…はっはっ、はっはっ、はっはっ…
Now, now... hah, hah, hah...
大丈夫か？だっ、はっ、はっ…
Is it okay? D- hah, hah...
この麺と、この海苔までは誰が来ても絶対忙しいからここまではやっておく。
Up to these noodles and seaweed, it'll be busy no matter who comes, so I'll prep them.
えっとで、ここにこれ売るだけで完食…
And then, just selling this here finishes it...
うまっ、うまっ…
So good, so good...
おい！ふざけんなマジ！
Hey! Are you fucking kidding me?!
ふざけんなっつってんだよ！
I said, are you kidding me?!
だって、待って、待って、待って！
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
はいというわけで、さっきはね、ちょっとモード間違えて始めてしまったので、
So anyway, earlier, I accidentally started in the wrong mode,
改めて、これ5分チャレンジだよね？やり直していきたいと思います。
so I'd like to restart properly with the 5-minute challenge.
さっき説明できなかったんですけど、もう一個気づいたことがあって、
I couldn't explain earlier, but I noticed something else.
このね、机のこの部分に残秒数がね、残り秒数が出てるんだわ。
On this part of the desk, the remaining seconds are displayed.
これをね活かして、あのせっかちないち、ロボットとかにね、先に出すなどね、ちょっと工夫してね、あの待つやつは待たせるみたいな感じでやっていきたいと思います。
So utilizing this, for impatient folks or robots, I want to manage who gets served first.
というわけで、5分チャレンジ、最後の挑戦、スタート！
With that, the 5-minute challenge, final try, start!
いくぞ！まず、まずはビールを冷やす。
Let's go! First, chill the beer.
まずはビールをとりあえず冷やしておいて、何本冷やすの？とりあえずいっぱいいっぱい冷やしといて。
First, let's get some beer chilling. How many? Just chill a bunch.
はい、何かな？はい、とりあえずもうこのね
Okay, what's next? Okay, for now, these...
ラーメン、汁、あっ、あっ、セーフ、汁麺、海苔まではみんな一緒なので、ここまではもうノーシーツで作っていきたいと、
Ramen broth, safe, broth, noodles, seaweed are the same for everyone, so I'll make those without thinking.
あっ、ビール、ビール、ビール！ビール2本。
Ah, beer, beer, beer! Two beers.
待っ、待っ…掴めない！お皿が邪魔で、どけ！
Wait, wait... I can't grab it! The plate's in the way, get out of here!
え、ビールを置いて、まずまたスクリーンショット撮って…
Uh, place the beer, take another screenshot...
ほらっ！
There!
えっと、でビールをとして…
And then, drop the beer...
ドアが開いててもさ、あぁ…ドアが開いててもさ…あ、餃子来た餃子！餃子きましたよ！
Even if the door is open... Ah... Even if the door is open... Ah, gyoza's here! Gyoza is here!
さあ、5、6！
Now, 5, 6!
で、ラーメンを、ノーシでラーメンを作って…
And make ramen, make ramen without thinking...
まじか！何回言ってんだおめぇ、ふざけんな！
Seriously! How many times are you gonna say that, dammit!
待って、待って！餃子が、餃子が壊れる！待ってさ、うい！
Wait, wait! The gyoza will break! Wait, ugh!
で、え、餃子、餃子はこうで…え、これができてます。
And, gyoza, gyoza goes like this... and it's done.
はいはい、餃子間に合ったかな？食べて、食べて！
Okay, okay, did I make it in time for gyoza? Eat, eat!
ナイス！
Nice!
うい！で、うい！で、ここまでノーシ！で、はい、これ入れて、はい、出来上がり！
Ugh! And, ugh! And, no thinking up to here! And, put this in, and it's done!
麺上がり！
Noodles ready!
えーっと、海苔と卵！はい、麺上がり！
Um, seaweed and egg! Yes, noodles ready!
餃子もやっとくか！3、4、5、6！
I'll prep gyoza too! 3, 4, 5, 6!
で、こうして、こうして、ここまでノーシ！
And, like this, like this, no thinking up to here!
で、えー、もうすぐできる！あー、はい、はい、はい…
And, um, almost done! Ah, yes, yes, yes...
吸い寄せて…あれっ、なんか2個足りない！
Pulling them in... Huh, I'm short two!
あっ！あと1個、まや！
Ah! One more, Maya!
ちょっと待って、液だんで卵！がんばれー！
Wait a sec, liquid... egg! Hang in there!
待て、化け物きてる、はい！
Wait, monster is coming, yes!
で、あぁ、餃子が！
And, ah, the gyoza!
セーフ！
Safe!
餃子、餃子できてますよ！
Gyoza, gyoza is ready!
はい！
Yes!
いや、どこ？あっ…
Wait, where? Ah...
あれっ、マリンの餃子！？
Huh, Marine's gyoza!?
ねぇなんで…？
Hey, why...?
なんで？さっきできたのに…
Why? It was just ready...
うるせぇ！！
Shut up!!
できた！はい！
Done! Yes!
いただきます！
Itadakimasu!
あっ待ってデブ、あぁデブに先に注文出すことになった、くそっ！
Ah wait, debu— ah, I ended up taking orders for the fat guy first, dammit!
女は待っとれ！
Women can wait!
待って、ロボットに、あぁデブ怒っちゃった。
Wait, for the robot— ah, the fat guy got mad.
餃子！ロボット早く作んないと。
Gyoza! Gotta make the robot's fast.
怒るぞあいつ！
He's gonna get mad!
待って、麺も入ってない！
Wait, noodles aren't in!
できた！
Done!
やばい、やばい！
Oh no, oh no!
回せー！
Spin it!
あぁー…ふふふふふ…
Agh... hahaha...
うわぁ、うまく行かない！卵がいかない！
Ugh, it's not going well! The egg isn't going!
やば！
Oh no!
まだペン点にしたくない！
I don't want to get penalized yet!
えっと、これでできてる…
Um, this is done...
あぁー、待って！
Agh, wait!
大丈夫！これで…
It's fine! With this...
まだ！まだ！まだ戦って！えっと、海苔、えっと、えっと、ねま…
Still! Still! Still fighting! Um, seaweed, um, um, nema...
ない！あっ、あった！はい！
None! Ah, found it! Yes!
じゃあ10秒！こうで、麺、ま…
Then 10 seconds! Like this, noodles, ma...
よし、いいぞ、いいぞ、いいぞ！
Alright, good, good, good!
セーフ、セーフ、セーフ！
Safe, safe, safe!
海苔！麺、ま…あっ、麺、ま溶けた！い！
Seaweed! Noodles, ma— ah, noodles melted! Yi!
はい、どうぞ！
Here you go!
ビールか！ビール、ビール！
Beer!? Beer, beer!
はい、ビール！どうぞ！
Yes, beer! Here you go!
いいよ、いいよ、いいよ、いいよ！
Good, good, good, good!
いいよ、いいよ！いい感じだよ！あぁー！
Good, good! Looking good! Agh—!
あぁ、何回くるんだよ！ぐれぇ！
Ah, how many times are you gonna come! Ugh!
えっと…ちょっと焦って…
Um... getting a bit flustered...
ロボットきたロボット！ロボットはね、早く出さないとね、こいつ…
Robot came, robot! If I don't serve the robot fast, this guy...
えっ、待っ…あ、いな、いな、いな、いな！いない！
Eh, wait— ah, he's not here, not here! Not here!
で、こうで、こうで！
And, like this, like this!
あっ！
Ah!
えっ？うそっ！うそっ！うそっ！
Eh? No way! No way! No way!
助けて！
Help me!
これ！用意して、用意して！
This! Prep it, prep it!
えで、よいしょ！あぁ溶け！
And, heave-ho! Ah, melted!
まってこうして…
Wait, like this...
あぁー！
Agh—!
はい！こうで、こうで！はいデブ！
Yes! Like this, like this! Yes, fat guy!
あっ、餃子、餃子！あと2個、あと2個！あと2個！
Ah, gyoza, gyoza! Two more, two more! Two more!
待って、また餃子きてる、また餃子きてる！
Wait, gyoza's coming again, gyoza's coming again!
がんばれー！
Hang in there!
ふぅ、ふぅ、ふぅ…
Whew, whew, whew...
焼けてねぇっ！焼けてない！焼けてない！
They're not grilled! Not grilled! Not grilled!
うざい、うざい、うざい！
Annoying, annoying, annoying!
この餃子もう、机のすべすべかす！
This gyoza, already— desk's getting messy!
あっ、怒った！
Ah, he got mad!
こう、こう、こう！5、6！えっと、で、ラーメンが、えっと、のりの…
Like this, like this, like this! 5, 6! Um, and, ramen, um, seaweed...
えー、で、間に合う！
Uh, and, I'll make it!
できてろ、できてろ、できてろ！
Be ready, be ready, be ready!
あっ！
Ah!
間に合いません！
I won't make it!
(Heavy breathing)
えっと、いま何てだった？いま何て？
Um, what was that just now? What just now?
早く…早く…
Hurry... hurry...
500…
500...
ということで…
So, uh...
ごめんな…
Sorry...
笑ってる、すがき、なとり持って笑っ…ごめん。
You were laughing, holding Sugakinatori, laughing... sorry.
お前を食わせて行きたかった…
I wanted to feed you before I went...
本日開店…
Today, opening...
ということで 本日閉店します。
So... today we are closing.
毎度ありがとうございましたー！！
Thank you as always!!
こ、ここは…？
Wh-Where is this...?
あ～良い夢見たのらぁ
Ah~ What a nice dream, nora.
みこち…！？みこち…？
Mikochi...!? Mikochi...?
あれ、あたしたちさっきまで…さっきまで確か…
Wait, until just a minute ago we were... I'm sure until just a minute ago...
「赤ちゃんプレイ」に勤しんでたはず…
We should have been engrossed in "baby play"...
ふぁっさ 赤ちゃんプレイしてたのら ふぁっさ
Fassa, we were playing babies, fassa.
ふぁっさ ふぁっさ
Fassa, fassa.
先輩たち 起きやがれこの野郎
Senpais, wake up, you bastards!
生意気だぞっちょっと先輩に向かって！ ふぁっさふぁっさ なんだその態度は！！
How cheeky, talking back to your senpais!! Fassa fassa, what is that attitude!!
我が名はねねち！
My name is Nenechi!
ここは天界である
This is heaven!
天界？ お前らは
Heaven? You guys are...
運動のしなさすぎで 死んだ
dead from lack of exercise!
頭おかしいのら？ なに言ってんだぁ？
Are you crazy, nora? What are you talking about?
死んだんだよぉ！！
You died!!
もう叩かれても痛くないからね おらっ
You won't feel pain even if you get hit now, take this!
本当だ！！ 死んでるぅぅぅぅぅ！！
It's true!! We're dead!!!!!!
うそっ おらっ あぁ…！
No way! Take this! Ah...!
本当だ！！
It's true!!
うそっ おらっ 痛くねぇ…
No way! Take this! It doesn't hurt...
みんな死んでるんだぁ！！！！
Everyone is dead!!!!
え、どうしたら生き返れるの！？ やだやだまだまだ！！
Eh, how can we come back to life!? No no no, not yet!!
まだホロライブにいたいよぉ～！！
I still want to be in Hololive~~!!
赤ちゃんプレイ早く続きしてぇのらぁ～
I want to continue the baby play soon, nora~
生き返る為には スポーツのテストを受けて
In order to come back to life, you must take a sports test...
成績が1位だった者のみ ねねが連れて帰る
and only the one who gets 1st place will Nene take back with her.
なぁんだってぇ～？ じゃあ…
What did you say~? Then...
え、じゃあ… 1位以外の人は…？
Eh, then... what about those other than 1st place...?
このまま死んだまま ここにず～っと居てもらう！！
You will stay here dead, forever!!
ここにず～っと居てもらう！！
You will stay here forever!!
いやでも待って！この二人には負けない… ねね先生おねがいしまぁ～す！！
Wait, wait! I won't lose to these two... Nene-sensei, please!!
うそっ すばらしい！ このババアの動き…
No way! Amazing! This hag's movements...
誰がBBAじゃっ デョウァアアア!!!!
Who's a hag?! Deoyaaaa!!!!
行くぞ！ついてこい！ついてこい！ふぁっさふぁっさふぁっさ
Let's go! Follow me! Follow me! Fassa fassa fassa
ここは！？ ここはどこだ！！
Where is this!? Where is this?!
なんなのらここはぁ～！
What is this place, nora~!
ここは今からみんなに競技してもらう会場だ！
This is the venue where everyone will now compete in sports!
なんだってぇ～！！
What did you say~~!!
まずはね、運動不足の君たちが怪我をしないように ストレッチをしていきたいと思う！
First, so that you unfit folks don't get hurt, we'll do some stretches!
めんどくせぇなぁ～
What a pain~
なんでそんなことしなきゃいけないんだよ
Why do we have to do that?
じゃあいきなりちょっと100mくらいずつ走っとくかみんな
Then let's suddenly run about 100 meters each.
クソザコにはキツイ距離
That's a tough distance for weaklings.
本日の種目 1.反復横跳び 2.バランス立ち 3.上体そらし 4.立ち幅跳び 5.バトルロワイヤルラン 6.上体起こし 7.ダンス
Today's events: 1. Side-to-side jumps 2. Balance stand 3. Back extension 4. Standing long jump 5. Battle Royale run 6. Sit-ups 7. Dance
足りてねぇのよ！足りねぇのが！
We're lacking! Lacking!
それではまず第1競技！はい！反復横跳びを行いたいと思います！
Now, for the first event! Yes! We will conduct side-to-side jumps!
え、やばい！
Eh, oh no!
忘れちゃった！
I forgot!
できる？
Can you do it?
ルール 1セット20秒で このちょっとみんなには見えないけど、この線を越える毎に1カウントずつ増えていく感じになります。
Rules: 20 seconds per set. You can't see it, but every time you cross this line, the count increases by 1.
得意なやつ来ました！！
My specialty is here!!
「ライン超え」
Crossing the line
先生のお手本をまず見せてもらえますか？
Could you show us the teacher's model first?
お、じゃあ… お願いします！
Ah, please!
それではねねちの反復横跳びね！
Now, Nenechi's side-to-side jumps!
スリー、ツー、ワン、ファイ
Three, two, one, fi-
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20...
早すぎる！早いすぎる！ガチやん！
Too fast! Too fast! That's for real!
早すぎる！
Too fast!
イェーイ！
Yay!
じゃあこれをね参考記録に。余裕だよねぇみんな！
Now, let's make this a reference record. Piece of cake right, everyone!
帰りたいもんでね、天界から！
We want to go home from heaven!
帰りたい！ 帰りたい！
I want to go home!
おろおろ…
Panicking...
じゃあやばいよやばいよ。ほら、本日セック…設営…
Then this is bad, this is bad. Look, today's sec... setup...
え、できるかな…？
Eh, can I do it...?
内股、内股！
Pigeon-toed, pigeon-toed!
じゃあ、船長の反復横跳びで！
Then, Captain's side-to-side jumps!
3、2、1、スタート！
3, 2, 1, Start!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10...
「横跳び」してなくねぇのら？
You're not doing "side jumps", nora?
え？なんこれ？え？してなくねぇのら？
Eh? What is this? Eh? You're not doing it, nora?
20、21、22、23、24、25…
20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25...
終わった終わった！ウータンみたいな動きやん！本気なの本気なの？
It's over! That looks like an orangutan! Are you serious?
ふざけてるのら？
Are you joking around, nora?
パンツが見えちゃう！パンツが見えちゃうよ！
Your panties are showing! Your panties are showing!
じゃあ船長の、えー、ライン超え回数は24回かな？
Then Captain's, um, line-crossing count is 24 times?
余裕じゃん！
Piece of cake!
盛り上がりが微妙すぎる。
The hype is way too weak.
はい、じゃあ次はみこせんぱい、いこう！
Okay, next is Miko-senpai, let's go!
みこせんぱい！
Miko-senpai!
みこせんぱい、いどみますよ！
Miko-senpai, challenge it!
お、余裕だね！
Oh, piece of cake!
じゃあみこせんぱいの反復横跳び、見せてみろ！
Then show us Miko-senpai's side-to-side jumps!
生きてみせる！
I'll survive!
3、2、1、スタート！
3, 2, 1, Start!
にっ、さん
2, 3...
あれ？これすごくない？
Wait, isn't this amazing?
すごいよ、すごいよ
Amazing, amazing!
12、13、14、15、16、17、18、19、20
12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20...
なんか遅くない？
Wait, isn't it slow?
18、19、20、21、22、23、24、25
18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25...
足が悲鳴をあげている…！！
My legs are screaming...!!
21、22、23、24、FINISH
21, 22, 23, 24, FINISH!
あれ、みこち！？w
Huh, Miko-chi!? lol
今のさあ、4回から1回越えてなくて…よくもイキってくれたな！！
Just now, you didn't even pass 4 and went to 1... How dare you act all cocky!!
行けえ！よくもイキってくれたな！
Take that! How dare you act so cocky!
マイナス分も合わせまして、結構23回かな？
Including the minus points, it's about 23 times?
何回だった？？
How many times was it??
（船長は）24回
(Captain) 24 times.
ええー！？
Eh?!
ああ～っはっはっは！マリン船長に負けてる～！
Ahahaha! You lost to Captain Marine!
フォームはみこ先輩の方が50倍くらいキレイだった
Miko-senpai's form was about 50 times prettier.
じゃあ最後、ルーナ先輩！ええ、現時点1位は24回の船長なんで、超えてってくださ～い。
Now last, Luna-senpai! The current 1st place is Captain with 24, so please surpass that.
ちょ、ルーナの、軽くライン超えていくのがな。
Heh, Luna easily crossing the line...
ルーナ先輩の反復横跳びまで、オッケー？
Until Luna-senpai's side-to-side jump, ready?
3、2、1、GO！
3, 2, 1, GO!
1、2、3、4、5、6、7、8、9、10…38、FINISH！
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10... 38, FINISH!
ルーナたん！！死んじゃったよぉ！
Luna-tan!! She died!!
本気出しちゃった…
She went all out...
まだ1回目なんだけどな、競技。えー、マイナスナシで、ルーナちゃんが38回が、
It's only the first event... Oh, with no minus points, Luna-chan got 38 times,
でも結果は、ルーナ先輩なんと38回！
But the result, Luna-senpai got an incredible 38 times!
いぇ～い！！
Yay!!
大丈夫？すごいよ！息がすごいよ！
Are you okay? That's amazing! You're so out of breath!
さあなんとね、今日は競技がいっぱいありますので、さっそく次の競技に移ります、みんな！
Well then, since there are many events today, let's move on to the next event, everyone!
でめちゃ大... 私ガチしんどいんだけどw
And it's super big... I'm actually exhausted lol
じゃあ次の競技、このままいきたいと思いますがい、次はね、簡単だよみんな！簡単？やった！
Now for the next event, we'll continue with this, but the next one is easy, everyone! Easy? Yay!
なんと簡単、次はね「バランス立ち」って、目を閉じてどれだけ片足でバランスを保っていられるか。
How simple, the next one is 'Balance Stand', where you close your eyes and see how long you can maintain balance on one foot.
なるほどね！じゃあみんなで、せーので目を閉じて片足立ちしただから、ルーナたんこっち。
I see! Then everyone, let's close our eyes and stand on one foot—Luna-tan, come here.
え、なんで？ え？ え、絵的にこうかなって。いくよ～！！
Eh, why? Eh? Eh, for compositional reasons. Here we go~~!!
せーの！っていったらみんなその場で手を、あ、足を持ち上げてください。はい！いきます。せーの！はい！
Ready, set! When I say that, everyone lift your hands, ah, your foot in place. Okay! Here we go. Ready, set! Go!
むし... 横は、だよ？ なんも考えてない。やめなよ、やめなよ！
Mushi... Beside you, okay? I'm not thinking anything. Stop it, stop it!
いやあぁぁぁぁぁ！！
Nooooooo!!
違う勝負してない？大丈夫？
Aren't you having a different match? Are you okay?
今の人が！！ルーナの妨害をしてきました！！！ルーナちゃんがみこのこと妨害してきました！ルーナちゃんがしてきた！私この人に妨害されました！
This person just interfered with Luna!! Luna-chan interfered with Miko! Luna-chan did it! I was interfered with by this person!
知らなもぉ～ん！！
I don't know anything~~!!
じゃあいきましょうみんな。はい、よーい！スタート！
Now let's go, everyone. Okay, ready! Start!
だめだよおっじゃあ。コアマッスルを意識して。いいね。コアマッスルを意識。コアマッスル？ちょっと...
No way, then. Be conscious of your core muscles. Good. Conscious of core muscles. Core muscles? Wait...
ばか！！体感！体感のチェックを。ガタガタガタガタ！
Idiot!! Core balance! Check core balance. Rattling rattling!
おれおれ、いい加減にして。ルーナ先輩も、ごたごたごたごた...
Hey hey, cut it out. Luna-senpai too, rumble rumble...
ああ～！情けないねぇ！！
Aah~! How pathetic!!
ちょっと押された程度でそんなフラフラしちゃってさぁ！
Getting pushed a little and wobbling around like that!
そんなに怒んないよ！
Don't get so angry!
あ、ざこざこざこざこ！うるせぇ！！ww
Ah, weakling weakling! Shut up!! lol
いぇ～い！！どうよ！？で結局優勝は…船長が１位！
Yay!! How's that!? So in the end, the winner is... Captain is 1st!
なにブーブーしてんのよ！
What are you grumbling about!
次がね「上体そらし」って言って、はーいはいはい。
The next one is called 'Upper Body Back Stretch', right right right.
寝ころうつぶせの状態で寝転んで、そっからこう反ってもらって、地面から何センチ顎が離れるかというのを測定したいと思います。
Lie down on your stomach, arch your back from there, and we'll measure how many centimeters your chin lifts off the ground.
おぉいいよいいよいいよ！これはどちらかというと体の柔らかさと、
Oh great great! This is more about body flexibility,
腹筋とか背筋の感じなのかな？
and ab/back muscle feel, right?
え、柔らかいわよ～マリン！上半身柔らかいよ。
Eh, I'm flexible~ Marine! My upper body is flexible.
よっしゃ、いくぞ！のりたい、のりたい！
All right, let's go! I want to ride, I want to ride!
のっちゃえ、のっちゃえ！え、みこち、ぬるの船長に！のっちゃえ！
Jump on, jump on! Eh, Miko-chi, step on Captain! Jump on!
せんせいはそんな上がらないの？
Sensei, you don't rise up that much?
わかんない。え、ちょっと！お尻叩かないで！！いやあ～！
I don't know. Eh, wait! Don't butt-slap me!! Nooo~!
可愛いってわけね。船上の状態そらし、スタート！
How cute. Captain's upper body back stretch, start!
あ！
Ah!
おっ、すごいすごい！
Oh, wow, wow, wow!
柔らかい！
Soft!
柔らかい柔らかい！
So soft!
早っ！早っ！
Hurry, hurry!
すごい！えっ？
Amazing! Eh?
53cm！
53 centimeters!
おっ、すごい！
Oh, wow!
柔らかっ！
So soft!
えっ？顔...
Eh? Face...
ぶっさあ！
Gross!
おい、降りろよ！おいこラァ！
Hey, get down already!
みこち！
Miko-chi!
じゃあ、じゃあ、みこち測っていこうか？
Then let's measure Miko-chi, shall we?
え、じゃあ今度はルーナ乗ってたい。
Then I want Luna to ride this time.
あーい。
Okay.
よーしと。
Here we go.
乗ってやるぜ。
I'm gonna ride ya!
やだぁ〜！
No way!
オムツがついちゃうよぉ！
It'll put diapers on me!
オムツじゃねぇのら〜！！
It's not a diaper!
じゃあ、準備できたところで、始めてくださーい！
Right, now that you're ready, begin!
はーい！
Yes!
３、２、１、スタート！
Three, two, one, go!
うわっ！
Whoa!
結構下がったわ！
She went back quite a bit!
勢い良かったけどさ。
Her momentum was good, though.
結構下がっちゃった。
She went too far back!
早い早い！
Fast, fast!
早っ早っ！
ここだから、
Because she's stiff,
35cmかな？
probably 35 centimeters?
だって、お風呂じゃん。
She just bathed in it!
はいはいはい、記録35cm！
Alright, let's see. Record is 35 centimeters!
しょぼぉ〜いw
How underwhelming!
ルーナ、今日できてたんだから。
Luna could do it, right?
じゃあずっと、ねねすぱ、ねね乗っていいかなあ...
So Luna, Nene can ride you too?
いいよ。
Sure.
姫様ルーナの体前屈、
Princess Luna's flexibility test,
スタート！
start!
いくのらぁ！
I'll do it!
覇気ないけど大丈夫？w
You lack spirit, but you'll be okay?
ふっ！
Hmph!
低くねぇぇ！？
Not low enough?!
もっと上がれだろ！
You can go higher!
頑張れ！頑張れ！
You can do it! Hang in there!
10cm！
10 centimeters!
はい、じゃあ結果出ましたね！
Right, results are in!
１位が船長で「53cm」！
First place is Captain with 53 centimeters!
次がみこ先輩の「35cm」！
Next is Miko-senpai with 35 centimeters!
で、ダントツ...
And by far...
最下位の「10cm」ルーナ先輩。
last place with 10 centimeters, Luna-senpai!
しかし続く立ち幅跳びでは...
However, in the standing long jump...
うぇっ！？
Whoa!
この人、カエルみたい。
She's like a frog!
うぇっ！？
Whoa!
すごーい！すごーい！
Amazing! Amazing!
ルーナが圧勝！！
Luna totally wins!!
こういう、可哀そうな人たちが...
Look at this pitiful sight.
バトルロワイヤルラン
Battle Royale Run
今からね、サバイバルランでみんなで勝負をしたいと思うの。
Now, we'll all compete in a survival run.
リズムに合わせて走ってもらうんだけど、
The rule is to keep running without falling behind the rhythm,
リズムに間に合わなかった場合、
if you can't keep up with the rhythm,
あと自分の体力限界になってしまった場合は、
or if your stamina hits zero,
その場でもバタッと...死んでしまうわけね！
you just drop dead right there!
死んでしまいます！
You die on the spot!
最終的まで残った人が勝利。
Whoever's left standing wins.
なるほど、簡単なのらねぇ。
I see, sounds simple.
余裕よ余裕！簡単でしょ！
This'll be a cinch!
みこち１回も１位になれてないからなぁ〜。
Miko-chi has never placed first, though.
そうなんだね！
That's true!
今回はね、ちょっと１位を取らせて頂きたいなと思っておりますよねぇ。
This time, I'd really love to take first place!
ムリムリw
No way.
まぁ、頑張ってよ！
Good luck!
じゃあ、やっていきましょう！
Alright, let's do this!
はい！GO！
Go!
いくのら？
Here we go?
なんか、先生余裕だぞ！！
The teacher's taking it so easy!
速い！
Faster!
行かないでみんな！
Don't leave me behind, everyone!
みんな死んでる！
Are they dying?
間に合ってる？w
Am I making it?
全く間に合ってません。
You're not making it at all!
あぁ、極楽...
Ah, so peaceful...
みんな死んじゃった！
Everyone's dead!
WIN！ルーナの勝ちー！
Luna wins!
みこちお前いいのかよ！！
Miko-chi, are you kidding me?
１回も１位になれないまま！！
You still haven't won a single time!
いやだぁぁぁぁ！
Nooo!
１位になりたいよぉ！
I wanna win!
今度は上体起こし！
Next is sit-ups!
今度こそ１位を取らせて頂きたいなと思っておりまーす！
I hope I can take first place this time.
じゃあ、ルーナの順番きたなこれ。
Well, Luna's turn has come.
絶対できねぇだろ！
There's no way she can do it!
体力の限界な！
She has no stamina!
50回やってやるから見てて！
I'll do 50, so watch me!
ハードル上げすぎでしょw
You're raising the bar too high!
え、何秒ですか？？
Eh, how many seconds?
30秒で、30秒で50回もできるわけないじゃん！！
30 seconds? Doing 50 in 30 seconds is impossible!
1秒間に2回やれば余裕なのら。
If you do two per second, it's a breeze.
先生の参考記録から見ましょうじゃあ。
Let's check the teacher's reference record, then.
あ、そうですね。
Oh, that's right.
頑張りましょう。
Let's do our best.
じゃあねねちの腹筋始めます！GO！
Nene-chi's abs, start!
１、２...
One, two...
速っ！
Fast!
なんか吸引してるみたい。
She looks like she's vacuuming!
キモいキモい！
It's gross!
キモい！
Gross!
やめなさい！！
Stop it!
ずっと続くじゃん！
It went on forever!
幸せなひと時だったね...
It was a happy moment...
時を忘れてずっとしてたね。
I forgot the time and just kept going.
何回か数えてた？
Were you counting?
いま何回だった？
How many was that?
え？
Eh?
すいません、船長もチューに夢中で
Sorry, Captain was also lost in the smooching
数えてませんでしたw
and wasn't counting!
ねねちの記録、「いっぱい」でお願いします！
Nene-chi's record is "lots"!
まだキスしてないじゃん
You still haven't kissed!
よし、いきましょう
Alright, let's go.
GO
いっ！いっ！あい！！！
1, 2, 3...!
声の勢いヤベェのらw
Her voice has so much energy, lol.
何なんの？
What is this?
まだ5回だよ！
That's only 5 times!
早く早く早く！
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
あと5回！3、2、1、FINISH!
5 more times! 3, 2, 1, FINISH!
はい、10回。
Yes, 10 times.
聞いて、笑われるからね、できなくなるから。
Listen, you're gonna get laughed at, you won't be able to do it.
覚えといて。
Remember that.
3秒に1回だったね、船長w
That's once every 3 seconds, Captain lol.
うるせぇ！w
Shut up! lol
じゃ、次、みこ先輩！
Next up, Miko-senpai!
みこ先輩だ！
It's Miko-senpai!
みこは本当に無理なんだよ。
Miko really can't do this.
船長の10回を笑えるようなレベルなのかな？
Can we really laugh at the Captain's 10 times?
うわぁぁぁぁぁぁぁぁ！
Waaaaah!
じゃ、いきまーす。
Alright, let's go.
GO!
がってないよ全然！！みこち！！！
You're not rising at all!! Miko-chi!!!
ちょっとみこち！！ちょっとみこち！！
Hey, Miko-chi!! Hey, Miko-chi!!
もう1回、もう1回！
One more time, one more time!
せーの、いーーーーーーっ！
Ready, oooooone!
手も頭から離れ…離して、離して！
Your hands came away from your head... Let go, let go!
本当に出来ないんだって！！せーの、いーーーーっ！
I really can't do it!! Ready, oooone!
毎回手こうなんのなにw
Why do your hands always do that lol
手ぷらされてるかのように。ヤッホー！
Like your hands are in tempura batter. Yahoo!
逃げるな！あと5秒、あと出るな！逃げるな！
Don't run away! 5 seconds left, don't get out!
この屈辱…！！
This humiliation...!!
0回！恥ずかしくないの、みこち？
0 times! Aren't you embarrassed, Miko-chi?
恥ずかしくないよ！恥ずかしくないよそんなんだもん！
I'm not embarrassed! I'm not embarrassed by something like this!
恥ずかしいよお！もうやだ！！ここにずっといるよおおお！！
It's embarrassing! I hate this!! I'm staying right hereeee!!
情けない結果ですけども。
Such a pathetic result though.
姫森ルーナがね、今からね、すごい。そう、2秒に1回やってくれるからね。
Princess Luna is gonna do it amazingly now. Once every 2 seconds.
そこに寝てる人いるのだけど？
There's someone sleeping over there, you know?
腹筋0回の人、どいてください。邪魔なんですけどぉ。
Person with 0 sit-ups, please move aside. You're in the way.
ヒデぇよ〜(泣)
That's harsh~ (crying)
はい、じゃあ、ルーナ先輩！
Alright then, Luna-senpai!
よーーーーい、おピースする余裕余裕だね。ピースまで。
Readyyy, giving a peace sign, she's so relaxed. Even a peace sign.
よーーーーい、スタート！
Readyyy, START!
いーっつぎ！おーい！うーん、チューチュー！
Oooone! Heeeey! Mmm, chuu chuu!
3、4、5、6、まんま、なんか余裕がある！
3, 4, 5, 6, wait, she actually has leeway!
チューチュー、チューシー、チューシー…？
Chuu chuu, chuushi, chuushi...?
10、11、12、13、うまっ！すご！
10, 11, 12, 13, wow! Amazing!
あれ、でも待って、あれ50回、あれ50回は？
Wait, hold on, what about 50 times?
18回！くっそ！余裕じゃなーい！
18 times! Damn it! Not easy at all!
仲間だと思ってたのに！一緒にしないで欲しいのら(笑)
I thought we were comrades! I don't want you grouping me with you (laughs)
ダンス！ルール：ねねのお手本を見たあとにどれだけ同じダンスを踊れるか競う
Dance! Rule: Compete to see how well you can dance Nene's choreography.
みこ先輩いいね！
Miko-senpai, nice!
みこ初勝利！！
Miko's first victory!!
お前腹筋0回だろ！！イッてんじゃねぇ！！
You have 0 sit-ups!! Don't get cocky!!
結果発表
Results Announcement
さあ、たくさん競技やってきましたが、1位を取れたのは結局誰だったのか！！
Now, we've done lots of events, but who actually took 1st place?!
というわけで、ねねと一緒に人間界に帰れるのは！？
Therefore, who gets to return to the human world with Nene!?
ルーーーナ！！WINNER 姫森ルーナ
RUUUUNA!! WINNER Himemori Luna
まあルーナ、よく言っていたのら。息切れは『演技』だと。
Well, Luna always said: Breathlessness is "acting."
めちゃくちゃ裏でバテ散らかしてたのに！！
Even though she was totally exhausted behind the scenes!!
じゃあルーナたん、人間界へ帰ろう！
Alright Luna-tan, let's return to the human world!
やだ！ずるい！いっぱいお菓子用意してるよ！
No way! Unfair! We've prepared tons of sweets!
来んじゃねぇ！！来んじゃねぇ！！ルーナたんキスするのら！
Don't come near us!! Don't come near us!! Luna-tan is gonna kiss us!
来んじゃねぇ！
Don't come near us!
みこにずっと一緒なんだね。そうだな、うちももうずっとここで二人きりなんだ。
You and Miko are always together. That's right, the two of us are gonna be alone here forever too.
仲良くしようも、ね？みこち一緒にここで赤ちゃんなるプレイしよう。
Let's get along, okay? Miko-chi, let's play being babies together here.
いやだ。
No way.
みこより体力あるやつと一緒に居れない！！んだよおお！！
I can't stay with someone who has more stamina than Miko!! What the hell!!
こっちだってこんなポンコツ暮らせるかよ！！
As if I could live with a useless piece of junk like you!!
んだよおい！
What the heck!
お前でかケツがぁ！
You big-assed—!
マリンちゃんスイッチ！
Marin-chan Switch!
宝鐘マリンちゃん（17歳）
Houshou Marine (17 years old),
天音かなたちゃんと一緒に、
together with Amane Kanata,
マリンが何のポーズをしているか当ててみてね！
guess what pose Marine is doing!
マリンちゃんスイッチ！
Marin-chan Switch!
あ…、あ…。え？これ何？
Ah... ah... Huh? What is this?
スケート？
Skating?
あれ、またひとりです。クリスマスなのに、あれ、あれ、
Huh, I'm all alone again. It's Christmas, yet, huh?
一人でスケートしに行くマリン。
Marine going skating all by herself.
あれれ？ひとりだぞ？
Huh? She's all alone?
なんだこのポーズ。一人でポーズをとっている。
What's with this pose? Posing all by herself.
アイドル！
An idol!
アイドルじゃねえだろ！
Like hell she's an idol!
なんだよさっきの、え、何そのポーズ。
What was that just now? Huh, what's that pose?
マリンちゃんスイッチ！
Marin-chan Switch!
い…。い、今度は当てるぞ。
I... I'll guess it this time.
胃が痛くて、胃が痛すぎるまである。胃が痛すぎるまで、あ、
My stomach hurts, to the point where it hurts so much. To the point where it hurts so—
なんこの手のもじゃもじゃは。い、いいんですか？そんなふ…。
What's with this fuzzy hand? Is... is this okay? Like this...
分かるわけねえだろ、イソギンチャク！
There's no way I'd know that, a sea anemone!
イソギンチャク見るでしょ、しかも。
You'd look at a sea anemone, plus—
マリンちゃんスイッチ、次ね、しかも。
Marin-chan Switch, next one, plus—
え？ちょっと雲行き怪しいんだけど。
Huh? Things are looking a bit sketchy.
埋もれとる。分かった！埋もれてる床に！埋もれたマリンも愛して。え、待ってこれ、ウゾームゾーじゃない？
Buried. I got it! Buried in the floor! Love the buried Marine too. Wait, isn't this writhing around?
分かった、ウゾームゾー。ウゾームゾー、ウゾームゾーにまぎれるマリン。
I get it, writhing. Writhing, Marine blending in with the writhing.
なんか撫で付けてる。ウゾームゾーのマリン。
She's patting herself down. Marine in the writhing.
おし…、わかんねえよ！
Butt... I have no idea!
埋もれたてのベイビー！ちょっと待て、おかしいんだ…。
A newborn baby! Wait a minute, this is weird...
マリンちゃんスイッチ！
Marin-chan Switch!
え？え？
Huh? Huh?
ああー、これは…。ストーカーすぎるな。
Ahh, this is... way too stalker-ish.
なんだこれ？え？え？まさか…。
What is this? Huh? Huh? No way...
盆踊りが、えっちっちのよいよいよい。
Bon Odori is ecchi-chi yoi yoi yoi.
どういうこと？近かったん盆踊り？え？まさか盆踊りかと思い…。
What do you mean? Was Bon Odori close? Huh? I thought it was Bon Odori...
はいはい。お、お尻じゃない？これ。
Yes, yes. Wh-isn't this an ass? This.
おしりを見ないでくださいね。おしりを見ないでください、マリンの。
Please don't look at my butt. Please don't look at Marine's butt.
お、お、近い近い近い！これ怒ってんじゃん！
Th-Th-Close, close, close! She's mad!
マリンちゃんスイッチ！
Marin-chan Switch!
なんだその顔は？なんでいちゃいちゃ見てくんのよ、こっち。
What's with that face? Why are you staring at me flirtatiously over here?
はい！ま…。まであるお。そこまで対応する、まであるを対応しすぎているまである。
Yes! Ma... to the max. Responding that much, over-responding to "to the max."
じゃねえこれ。まざいの方か！まざいか！まざい！
That's not it. Mazai! Mazai! Mazai!
まであるかと思った。まざい！まざい！まであるかと思った。
I thought it was "to the max." Mazai! Mazai! I thought it was "to the max."
疲れましたね。
I'm exhausted.
もう勘弁してくれ…。もう…。
Give me a break already... Jeez...
もうどんどんちょっとカメラ引いてカメラ引いて、もうマリンをつないで、もう疲れきった。ちょっと本当にタオルがほしい。完じゃない！
Just keep pulling the camera back, pull the camera back, connect Marine, I'm totally exhausted. I really want a towel. That's not "The End"!
お母さん…。何してるの…？
Mother... What are you doing...?
違うの、違う、違う、あくあは違う。全然違うのあくあ。これにはわけがあるの。
No, no, no, Aqua, it's not like that. It's completely different, Aqua. There's a reason for this.
ないけどあるの、あくあ。
There isn't, but there is, Aqua.
お母さん…。あたしの彼氏に…手出したの！？
Mother... Did you make a move... on my boyfriend!?
いやぁ、マリンが俺サマを誘惑してきたからつい…。
Well, Marine seduced me, so...
黙っててシオン！！
Shut up, Shion!!
間違えた。黙ってなさい、シオンくん。
My bad. Shut your mouth, Shion-kun.
最低…。お母さん最低だよ！！
Despicable... Mother, you're despicable!!
浮気性のシオンはともかく、お母さんそんな人だったなんて…！！
Leave aside the cheating Shion, I can't believe Mother was that kind of person...!!
あたしの彼氏と「出航」するような、そんな女だったなんて！！
To think you're the kind of woman who'd "set sail" with my boyfriend!!
あくあ落ち着いて、あなた誤解してるの。あなたのお母さんがそんなことするわけないでしょう？
Aqua, calm down, you're misunderstanding. Your mother would never do something like that, right?
シオンくんの目にゴミが入ってたからちょっと出航しただけ。
Some dust got in Shion-kun's eye, so I just set sail for a moment.
してない、してない、してない、嘘、嘘、出航しないわあくあ。お母さんのこと信じられるわよね？
I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, lies, lies, I won't set sail, Aqua. You can trust your mother, right?
お母さんのバカ！！
You idiot, Mother!!
オバサンのくせに若い子と出航なんかして、恥ずかしくないのぉ！？
For an old hag setting sail with a young person, aren't you ashamed!?
しかも、あたしの彼氏となんて！！
And with my boyfriend, of all people!!
オバサンのくせにみっともない！！恥知らず！もう裏切り者！お母さんの…
For an old hag, how pathetic!! Shameless! Traitor! Mother's...
ううううううるっせえええええ！！！！
Shuuuuuuuuut up!!!!!
誰がババアだこのオマ…！ガキの癖に一丁前にオンナみたいなこと抜きやがってよぉ！
Who's an old hag, you bi—! Acting all grown up for a brat, pulling woman-like stunts!
イライラする！まだそんな歳じゃないのに！マリンちゃんイライラする！
It's so annoying! I'm not even that old yet! Marin-chan is so irritated!
誰が今まで育ててやったと思ってんだよぉ！！
Who do you think raised you up until now!!
娘の彼氏のひとりやふたり、つまみ食いしたってバチ当たらねぇだろうがよぉ！
Nibbling on one or two of your daughter's boyfriends shouldn't bring any bad karma!!
なによ！悪いことしたのはお母さんなんでしょう！？
What is this! The one who did something wrong is Mother, right!?
これ以上あたしの彼氏に手出さないで！！
Don't you dare touch my boyfriend any more than this!!
いやですううう～シオンはお母さんの彼氏ですうう～
No wayyy~ Shion is Mother's boyfriend~
だいたいあんた…
Mostly you...
どうせまだ出航してないんでしょう～??
You still haven't set sail, have you??
――っしし…
Hehehe...
してます けどぉお!? (嘘)
I have, though!? (Lie)
してないんだぁ～ww
You haven't at all~~! ww
あれぇ～??
Huh...??
お母さんはもうしましたけど～??
Mother already did~~??
出会って5秒で即出航しましたけどぉ～??ｗ
We met and set sail 5 seconds later, though~~ww
このクソBBAァァ!!!!
You old haggg-!!!!
おいふたりとも!
Hey, both of you!
俺サマは複数人同時に攻略出来るから心配するなよ
I can conquer multiple people at once, so don't worry!
うるさい!! シオンは黙ってて!!
Shut up!! Shion, be quiet!!
なんか落としちゃったぁ(棒)
Whoops, I dropped something (deadpan).
まごまごぺろぺろ…
Mago, mago, pero, pero...
あ、ちょっと！
Ah, wait!
それはみこ部長の作った変な薬!!
That's Miko-buchou's weird medicine!!
おかゆ…!!
Okayu...!!
おかゆ、だめ！
Okayu, don't!
おかゆ 早く吐きなさい!!
Okayu, spit it out right now!!
ボクで良くな～い?
Wouldn't I be fine instead~?
おかゆがこんなに素敵なケモミミ美男(美少女)だったなんて…!!
To think Okayu was such a wonderful cat-eared bishounen...!!
もうほかの男なんかどうでもいいっ!!!
Who cares about other guys!!!
マリン、おかゆと出航したい!!
Marine, I want to set sail with Okayu!!
いいよ～
Sure thing~
だめよ! 元々おかゆはあたしが飼ってたんだから!!
No way! Originally, I was the one raising Okayu!!
おかゆはあたしのよ!!
Okayu is mine!!
やだねぇ~
No way~
おい 何言ってんだッ!
Hey, what are you saying?!
こんな良いケモミミオンナ 俺サマのもんに決まってるだろ!?
Such a good cat-eared girl is obviously mine, right?!
そうとも言えるねぇ
You could say that, too~
ちょっと、あたしが元々飼い始めたんだからあたしのだって…
Wait, I was the one who started keeping her first! Mine is--
ちょっと おかしいって！
Hey, stop it!
やめろよ! お母さんと行こうよ！
Come on, let's go with Mother!
なんだこいつ！
What's with this guy?!
うるせぇ！
Shut up!
マリンちゃん!!!
Marine-chan!!
本当に… 悪かったにぇ!!
I'm truly sorry, I was wrong!!
本当に僕のことを愛してくれていたのは 君だけだったと――
That the only one who truly loved me was you—
あれっ
Huh?
あっ!? あれ～!!?
Ah...?! Huh?!
もしかして僕の研究が… 完成していたのか!!
Could it be that my research was... complete?!
これは… 僕が大好きな ケモミミ美少女だにぇええ!!
This is... the cat-eared bishoujo I love so much!!
うるせぇクソジジイ!!!
Shut up, you old geezer!!!
おかゆに触ってんじゃねぇ!!
Don't touch Okayu!!
おにぎり買いに行ってきま～す
I'm going to go buy some onigiri~
ぜっっぜん許すまじ!
No way I'm forgiving you!
みこちゃん!
Miko-chan!
やめて! ぶ!
Stop, don't!
タピオカ
Tapioca
タピオカ、タピオカ、飲み込んでるから、ごろごろ…
Tapioca, tapioca, I'm swallowing it, so goro-goro...
ひどい…
Awful...
なんでみんなマリンを裏切るの?
Why does everyone betray Marine-chan?!
こんなに溺愛してるのに…
Even though I'm spoiling her this much...
どこだ…!?w
Where is it...?! w
何がどこだって?
What, what is where?
あ、お母さん、私自分の部屋掃除してくるから、それまでリビングに
Ah, Mother, I'm going to clean my own room, so until then, in the living room...
「シオンちゃん」に… あ、シオンちゃんじゃないか…
To "Shion-chan"... ah, not Shion-chan?
あ、ごめん!
Ah, sorry!
向き調整中
Adjusting direction...
おかゆがこんなに素敵なケモミミ美男(美少女)だったなんて!!
To think Okayu was such a wonderful cat-eared bishounen...!!
もうほとほ…
I'm almost...
なんて言った?
What did she say?
声優だぞ
She's a seiyuu, though.
マリンちゃん…
Marine-chan...
ごめん…
I'm sorry...
マリン船長の番組
Captain Marine's Show
宝鐘マリン×Yunomi オリジナル楽曲
Houshou Marine x Yunomi Original Song
6名の新進アニメーターさんたちのアニメミュージックビデオを載せて、このあと22時プレミア公開!
Animation PV by 6 motion animators coming out at 22:00 today!
1回見ても聞いても理解できない不思議な曲です。
It's a mysterious song that you can't quite understand even if you listen and watch it once.
君の頭を制服する、触手トラックになりたい!
I want to become a seifuku-wearing, brainwashed tentacle truck!
宝鐘マリン 2周年グッズのご告知です。
Houshou Marine 2nd Anniversary Goods Notice!
まずは こちら、キャンバスアートです!
First is the Canvas Art!
続いて、だいぶ前に君たちから提案いただいた… 提案された…
Next, the pirate flag proposed by you guys some time ago...
海賊旗もついにグッズにしてみました!
The Pirate Flag has finally been turned into goods!
部屋に飾ればそれだけで、そう。
Just hanging it in your room makes...
そこは宝鐘海賊団の船になるのだ!
That becomes the Houshou Pirates' ship!
そしてこちら、船長が胸につけているバッチとおそろいのネクタイピンです。
And this is the matching Necktie Pin that the Captain wears on her chest!
えっ、ネクタイつけてないよ、っていう君も、
Even if you're like, "Eh, I don't wear neckties,"
これを部屋に置いておけば、
if you keep this in your room,
もう船長、忘れものして… と何かあった一夜を演出できますね!
Captain Marine can pull a "memories forgotten" and you can stage a scene that happened one night!
全部セットでご購入いただきましたらば、
If you purchase the complete set,
こちらのご感想… ポストカードがついてきます!
this postcard will be included!
ポストカード、集めてますよね?
You collect postcards, right?
目指せ全集コンプ!
Aim to be a complete-set cup!
以上、グッズご告知でした!
That's all for the goods notice!
はい、最後のお知らせです。
And finally, a notice!
船長とフブキちゃんのネットラジオ、
Captain and Fubuki-chan's net radio,
Vのすこんなオタ話なんだ!
V no Sconbu Otahan Nanda!
なんかなんだわ
What is this all about?
本日8月11日配信の回にて、
On today's August 11th broadcast,
なんと、サプライズで
incredibly, as a surprise,
船長の愛する「サクラ大戦」李紅蘭役の
for the Captain, from Yuriko Fuchizaki-sama,
渕崎ゆり子さまからメッセージをいただいてしまいました！
who voices Koran Ri in her beloved Sakura Wars!
なぜかなんだかフブちゃんがやってくれたらしくて
Apparently Fubuki-chan set it all up somehow,
なんかあの、あの、マリンちゃんにサプライズしてって、ありがとうフブちゃん！
surprising Marine-chan, thank you Fubuki-chan!
ということで、えー超貴重な音源、
So, for just one week, you can hear
発狂する船長を聞けるのは1週間、君たちもこの喜びをぜひとも聞いてください！
the Captain losing her mind over this rare audio!
以上告知でした！
That's all for the announcement!
それでは22時の船長のプレミア公開でお会いしましょう、出航ー！
See you at the 22:00 premiere, set sail!